{
    "id": "76f591c875944bacbce8b86699efd7ad",
    "title": "Gerund or infinitive – grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e59593d7fc9f4ce78167f1970cb60681",
            "title": "Gerund Or Infinitive",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have …………………. soon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to go",
                        "going"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They refused …………………… the matter any further.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to discuss",
                        "discussing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He threatened ………………… me if I didn’t give him the key.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to shoot",
                        "shooting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I promise …………………… you tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visiting",
                        "to visit"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He intends …………………… a business.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to start",
                        "starting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher taught the children …………………  the truth.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to tell",
                        "telling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Jack told me …………………… dressed in ten minutes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to get",
                        "getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Susie wishes ………………… music.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to learn",
                        "learning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He learned ………………….. English in six months.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to speak",
                        "speaking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I dared him ……………………  across the river.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "jumping",
                        "to jump"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}